

### PERSONAL INFO

I am a very responsible and flexible person. Always open to new experiences. I enjoy helping others achieve their goals; Furthermore, working with people has always been my strongest point.

A safe and good working environment is the key to successful work.

# **LANGUAGES**

- Dutch (mother tongue)
- English (excellent)

# **CONTACT INFO**





01-09-1995

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Alight**

01-02-2023 - Currently

-Payroll specialist
-HR assistant

### **Eva Global**

20- 02- 2022 - 31-12-2022

- -Technical support
- -Customer service

#### Vattenfall Nederland

12-03-2018 - 08-06-2021

- Personal advisor
- Client guidance in financial matters
- -Sales

## **Essent**

03-05-2015-02-01-2017

- Sales employee

# **EDUCATION**

# Stedelijk college Zoetermeer

Sport and movement

#### **ROC** Leiden

Sport and movement